this here
key on the door,
my things here were not open,
leave this camera hidden to see what he's talking about.
is that I forgot to speak to you.
it's all open here in the wardrobe,
but I wanted you not to mess with my stuff,
you know?
it is not 1/4 private,
it was supposed to be a private room,
right?
there I come
my stuff is all open
then it comes here it opens it moves my thing
you're seeing my thing
and you have my privacy yes,
it's ok you're not seeing everything there you're seeing now
yes,
but leave it open to get air so it doesn't mold,
okay?
but then you ask me to leave it open,
no need
I came to open my legs,
it's you who opens,
I know it closes,
but it is.
okay, okay
today is the seventy-two,
pay for what was,
it's all right,
I leave the key for you here
we close.
I stepped on my foot bro
goal
anytime
She Goes Away.
now i need to deliver truffle,
it's Poze guys,
we are too good
now I'm getting a ride with the Rafa of convenience.
thank you Rafa,
Thanks,
Valeu mano,
Thanks.
the guy comes to get the truffle noise and steal the truffle
oh well myself,
all good.
O bro sorry for the delay then I had a,
I'm going to put the truffles here quickly bro,
okay,
then stay with God, bro.
Good Rest over there,
all good?
good weekend.
I meant,
wait bro,
hi,
Juninho put his father on the broom here,
Or came to get it.
I go there,
I'm going down.
sometimes
the signs of life take you
for some things that
we cannot ignore.
Is it on?
days left for me to open the deal.
probably
the money I
accumulated so far is still not enough bro.
from now on I'm going to have to be more strategic
in my ideas
and think about how to make it work.
but I think I had 1 idea.